var quizQuestions = [
    {
        type: "Emotion",
        content: "Worried => 心配する (shinpai suru)",
        question: "Worried",
        correctAnswer: "心配する (shinpai suru)",
        possibleAnswer: ["心配する (shinpai suru)", "不安な (fuan'na)", "混乱した (konran shita)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Emotion",
        content: "Laugh => 笑い (warai)",
        question: "Laugh",
        correctAnswer: "笑い (warai)",
        possibleAnswer: ["興奮した (kōfun shita)", "驚き (odoroki)", "笑い (warai)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Emotion",
        content: "Shout => 叫ぶ (sakebu)",
        question: "Shout",
        correctAnswer: "叫ぶ (sakebu)",
        possibleAnswer: ["怖い (kowai)", "叫ぶ (sakebu)", "怒り (ikari)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Family",
        content: "Child => 子供 (kodomo)",
        question: "Child",
        correctAnswer: "子供 (kodomo)",
        possibleAnswer: ["子供 (kodomo)", "赤ちゃん (akachan)", "子供達 (kodomodachi)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Family",
        content: "Parents => 両親 (ryoushin)",
        question: "Parents",
        correctAnswer: "両親 (ryoushin)",
        possibleAnswer: ["カップル (kappuru)", "夫婦 (fūfu)", "両親 (ryoushin)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Family",
        content: "Son => 息子 (musuko)",
        question: "Son",
        correctAnswer: "息子 (musuko)",
        possibleAnswer: ["姪 (mei)", "子供 (kodomo)", "息子 (musuko)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Food",
        content: "Beef => 牛肉 (gyūniku)",
        question: "Beef",
        correctAnswer: "牛肉 (gyūniku)",
        possibleAnswer: ["牛肉 (gyūniku)", "鶏肉 (toriniku)", "豚肉 (butaniku)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Food",
        content: "Japanese food => 日本食 (nipponshoku)",
        question: "Japanese food",
        correctAnswer: "日本食 (nipponshoku)",
        possibleAnswer: ["洋食 (yōshoku)", "中華料理 (chūkaryōri)", "日本食 (nipponshoku)"]
    },
    {
        type: "Food",
        content: "Milk => ミルク (miruku)",
        question: "Milk",
        correctAnswer: "ミルク (miruku)",
        possibleAnswer: ["チーズ (chīzu)", "ミルク (miruku)", "ヨーグルト (yōguruto) "]
    },
    {
        type: "Food",
        content: "林檎 (ringo) => Apple",
        question: "林檎 (ringo)",
        correctAnswer: "Apple",
        possibleAnswer: ["Orange", "Grapes", "Apple"]
    }
];
  
  export default quizQuestions;